 "quiz": {
        
        "maths": {
            "q1": {
                "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "12"
            },
            "q2": {
                "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
                ],
                "answer": "4"
            }
			"q3": {
                "question": "12 / 2 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "1",
                    "6",
                    "9",
                    "4"
                ],
                "answer": "6"
            }
			"q4": {
                "question": "12 * 2 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "18",
                    "20",
                    "31",
                    "24"
                ],
                "answer": "24"
            }
			"q5": {
                "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
                ],
                "answer": "4"
            }
			"q6": {
                "question": "12-8+2 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "11",
                    "6",
                    "3",
                    "14"
                ],
                "answer": "6"
            }
			"q7": {
                "question": "6 + 12 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "7",
                    "22",
                    "12",
                    "18"
                ],
                "answer": "18"
            }
			"q8": {
                "question": "4+6+1+5 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "16",
                    "12",
                    "17",
                    "15"
                ],
                "answer": "16"
            }
			"q9": {
                "question": "40-10 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "31",
                    "29",
                    "30",
                    "41"
                ],
                "answer": "30"
            }
			"q10": {
                "question": " 8*2 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "16",
                    "12",
                    "32",
                    "42"
                ],
                "answer": "16"
            }
        }
    }